1000freeads.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

 **PostAllAds4Free.com   PRIVACY POLICY**

PostAllAds4Free.com has established this privacy policy to explain to you how your information is protected, collected and used, which may be updated by PostAllAds4Free.com from time to time. PostAllAds4Free.com will provide notice of materially significant changes to this privacy policy by posting notice on the PostAllAds4Free.com site.

**PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY**

We don’t share your information with third parties for marketing purposes. We don’t engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other sites. We don’t employ tracking devices for marketing purposes (“cookies”, “web beacons,” single-pixel gifs). We don’t send you unsolicited communications for marketing purposes. We offer email anonymization & relay, to reduce 3rd party harvesting & spam. PostAllAds4Free.com, may provide links to third party websites, which may have different privacy practices. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited. PostAllAds4Free.com is not responsible for any kind of dealings between buyers and sellers.

**DATA WE COLLECT**

We sometimes collect your email address, for purposes such as sending self-publishing and confirmation emails and providing subscription email services etc. We may collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds or interactive forums, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on PostAllAds4Free.com that you expect to keep private. Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administrator the PostAllAds4Free.com site, and to otherwise provide our service to you.

Copyright © 2017 PostAllAds4Free.com. Post ads for free. Online advertising. Free classified ads online
